http://www.ls.cc.al.us/discover_lscc/public_relations/privacy_policy.aspx

Graduation 2020
Contact Us!
Consumer Information
Request a Tour
Tell A Friend about LSCC
Apply Now!
Lawson State Facts!
LSCC Retention Data
Student Achievement
Get the LSCC Free App!
QEP: R.A.C.E
QEP: Student Advising Hub
QEP: Registration Portal
Everything QEP
Contact Us!
About the Q.E.P
ADMISSIONS & RECORDS
Admissions Office & Records Office (Home Page)
Transcript Requests
Contact an Enrollment Specialist!
Admissions Information
Admission Procedures for All Students
Admissions Appeals (Suspensions)
International Students
Non High School Graduates (ATB)
Transient Students
Tuition Management System (TMS)
Exam Schedule
Forms (Online)
Scholarship Information
Student Records Policy (FERPA)
Tuition and Fees
Announcements
Register Now!
Dual Enrollment
Dual Enrollment (Start Here!)
GED
Apply Now!
FINANCIAL AID
Financial Aid (Home Page)
Getting Started!
Official Withdrawal
Unofficial Withdrawal (Dropping Out)
60% Date
Apply Now!
STUDENT SERVICES
Student Services (Home Page)
ASPIRE 2030: Student Success Committee
Bookstore, Police (On Campus Services)
Counseling Seminars, Activities & Events
Disability Services (ADA)
Meet & Contact ADA Counselors
Prospective Students (Start Here!)
Student Responsibilities
Faculty & Staff (ADA Resources)
TRiO Programs (SSS and Upward Bound)
Testing and Assessment Services
Ability to Benefit
American College Test (ACT)
Accuplacer
ACT Residual Testing
CAAP
Bootcamp (Online)
Housing and Residential Life
HOUSING Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ's)
RA Incident Reporting Form
Support Resources (for Students)
Disability (ADA)
Libraries
Space Center (Retention, Tutoring, Counseling)
Technical Support Helpdesk
Online Tutoring Center
TRIO Programs (Upward Bound & SSS)
Title IX--Everything You Need to Know
Title IX: Video (Facts)
Health Professions Programs
All Programs (Listing)
Dual Enrollment
CTEL Training (Register Here)
Honors College
STARS
Apply Now!
HR Forms
New Employees (Start Here!)
Employee Tuition Waiver
ADA (Employee Information)
Faculty & Staff Training
Adjunct Faculty (Requirements)
ATHLETICS
Athletics (Home Page)
Vendor Forms
Direct Deposit Information (for Students)
VIRTUAL ADVISING CTR.
MyLAWSON
CAMPUS!
BLACKBOARD
EMAIL LOGIN
STUDENT SUITE
FACULTY SUITE
HELP DESK (Technical Support)
DISCOVER LSCC
Home
»
DISCOVER LSCC
»
Graduation 2020
Contact Us!
Consumer Information
Request a Tour
Tell A Friend about LSCC
Apply Now!
Lawson State Facts!
Get the LSCC Free App!
QEP: R.A.C.E
Apply Now!
Click to Register !
z
Why A Privacy Policy?
Lawson State Community College respects your individual privacy. This Privacy Policy ('Policy') embodies our commitment to its protection through adherence to fair electronic information practices. This Policy puts you, the individual, in control of how your personal information is processed. You have our promise that we will not electronically process your personal information in any way that is incompatible with this Policy.
This Privacy Policy protects your privacy by:
Informing you about:
The types of personal information Lawson State Community College collects about you through its Web Site;
How it collects that information;
The general purposes for which it collects such information;
The choices and means by which individuals may limit its use and disclosure.
Empowering you to choose:
Whether and how certain personal information you provide is used (where such use is unrelated to the uses for which you originally disclosed it); and
Assuring you that Lawson State Community College :
Takes reasonable precautions to protect personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction;
Implements reasonable policies and procedures to ensure that personal information is kept only for the purposes for which it has been gathered;
Uses reasonable measures to ensure that we have accurately and completely recorded the personal information you have provided; and
Provides you reasonable access to your personal information as well as procedures for correcting or modifying that information where appropriate.
Ensuring accountability to individuals who believe that Lawson State Community College has not complied with these privacy principles.
The information we receive from or about you is stored on systems designed to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of that information. We also encrypt your transmission of sensitive information to us in the interest of heightened privacy protection and information integrity.
Our Accountability to You
In addition to the privacy protections that we provide, our employees, agents and business partners are independently responsible for ensuring compliance with this Privacy Policy, as described below.
If you feel that Lawson State Community College, or any of our agents, representatives or employees, is violating this Privacy Policy, please contact us via e-mail at privacy@lawsonstate.edu, by telephone at (205) 925-2515, or by postal mail at:
Lawson State Community College
Attention: WebMaster
3060 Wilson Road
Birmingham, AL 35221
(205) 925-2515
Notification of Changes
We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy 30 days before their effective date so you will always know what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. You are responsible for periodically checking our web site for changes to this Privacy Policy. You may opt-out of any posted change to our collection, use or disclosure of your personal information by sending an e-mail to privacy@lawsonstate.edu
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact privacy@lawsonstate.edu
College Accreditations:
Lawson State Community College is accredited by the Commission on Colleges of the Southern Association of Colleges and Schools to award the associate degree and certificates.  Contact the Commission on Colleges at 1866 Southern Lane, Decatur, Georgia 3033-4097 or call 404-679-4500 for questions about the accreditation of Lawson State Community College.
Alabama Board of Nursing ~ National League for Nursing
Accrediting Commission
Association of Collegiate Business Schools and Programs ~
Council on Occupational Education
Air Conditioning and Refrigeration Institute ~ American Dental Association
American Welding Society ~ National Automotive Technicians
Education Foundation, Inc. (NATEF)
